Extreme violence. Bad language. And a bloody good time.
Mortal Kombat Legends: Scorpion's Revenge is a animation,
action, fantasy film directed by Ethan Spaulding.
After the vicious slaughter of his family by stone-cold mercenary
Sub-Zero, Hanzo Hasashi is exiled to the torturous Netherrealm.
There, in exchange for his servitude to the sinister Quan Chi, he’s given a chance to avenge
his family – and is resurrected as Scorpion, a lost soul bent on revenge.
Back on Earthrealm, Lord Raiden gathers a team of elite warriors – Shaolin monk Liu Kang, Special Forces officer
Sonya Blade and action star Johnny Cage – an unlikely band of heroes with one chance to save humanity.
To do this, they must defeat Shang Tsung’s horde of Outworld
gladiators and reign over the Mortal Kombat tournament.
Hanzo Hasashi / Scorpion (voice), played by Patrick Seitz.
Liu Kang (voice), played by Jordan Rodrigues.
Sonya Blade (voice), played by Jennifer Carpenter.
Johnny Cage (voice), played by Joel McHale.
Jax Briggs (voice), played by Ike Amadi.
Sub-Zero (voice), played by Steve Blum.
Scorpion is a  character in the Mortal Kombat fighting game
franchise by Midway Games and NetherRealm Studios.
A ninja dressed in yellow, his primary weapon is a rope
dart, which he uses to harpoon opponents.
Since his debut in the original 1992 game, Scorpion has appeared as a playable
character in every main installment except Mortal Kombat 3 (1995).
The series' original Scorpion is Hanzo Hasashi (Japanese: 波佐志 半蔵), an undead Japanese warrior
principally defined by his quest to avenge the deaths of himself, his family, and his clan.
After the death of Bi-Han / Sub-Zero, Hasashi develops a feud with who he believed to be the killer, Bi-Han's younger brother and second
Sub-Zero, Kuai Liang, that spans most of the franchise before discovering the sorcerer Quan Chi is the real murderer.
While Hasashi has been depicted as a neutral figure focused primarily on seeking
revenge, he will side with those who can help him achieve his goals.
Following two reboots, Kuai Liang (Chinese: 奎凉; pinyin: Kúi Liáng) becomes the new Scorpion in Mortal
Kombat 1 (2023), while alternate timeline variants of Hasashi make minor appearances.
Scorpion has remained a pop culture icon, receiving critical acclaim since his
debut and frequently appears in media outside of the games.
The film explores themes of magic, ninja fighter, revenge, sorcerer, tournament.